[
==============================================================================================================================================================================================================================](https://www.schoolday.com/)

[
==============================================================================================================================================================================================================================](https://www.schoolday.com/)

Privacy & Terms
---------------

Last updated: June 15th, 2023

### School Day Services

**Introduction**

SchoolDay LLC and its affiliates (“School Day, “we”, “us”) is committed to protecting and respecting privacy and the protection of information that identifies, relates to, describes, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with an individual natural person or, where applicable, a household (“Personal Information”). This Statement explains our approach with respect to Personal Information we collect in connection with providing educational wellbeing survey services (the “Services”), as further described in our Terms of Service \[[https://schoolday.fi/en/community/school-day-privacy#tos](https://www.schoolday.com/en/community/school-day-privacy#tos) \], to our customers that provide public and private education services (each a “Customer”).

**How Does School Day Obtain Personal Information And What Personal Information Do We Obtain?**

In connection with providing the Services, we receive certain information relating to our Customers’ students (collectively “Users”). This information may constitute Personal Information under applicable laws.

The information may include:

* E-mail address;
* A device ID;
* An IP address;
* Software-based analytics information such as information about how a User uses the Services; and
* Username and passwords.

When you use the Services, we also store information about Users’ use of the Service, such as answers to questions provided in the Services.

We process the Personal Information collected in connection with the Services pursuant to the service agreement we have in place with our Customers and in accordance with the legal basis that our Customers process the Personal Information. To the extent that the legal basis for processing Personal Information is consent, you can withdraw your consent at any time by informing the Customer you provided your consent to or by emailing us at [privacy@schoolday.com](mailto:privacy@schoolday.fi).  The withdrawal of your consent does not affect the lawfulness of processing of Personal Information before such withdrawal.

**For What Purposes Is Personal Information Used?**
---------------------------------------------------

We use the Personal Information collected about Users in connection with the Services for the following purposes:

* To provide the Services;
* To anonymize, pseudonymize, and aggregate Personal Information;
* To perform visitor tracking and data analysis;
* To enable third-party analytics; and
* To support our business analysis and overall operations, as well as business intelligence, product development, product and service improvement, and content customization

**How Does School Day Disclose Personal Information to Third Parties?**
-----------------------------------------------------------------------

We may disclose the Personal information collected about Users in connection with the Services with the following categories of third parties:

* Service providers, such as data storage service providers and data analytics service providers.

We may also disclose Personal Information to:

* Public authorities, such as law enforcement, if we are legally required to do so or if we need to protect our rights or the rights of third parties; and
* Our subsidiaries and affiliates; or a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of our services and their advisors in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of our stock and/or assets, or in connection with bankruptcy proceedings, or other corporate reorganization.

**Your Rights Relating to Personal Information**

We take steps to help ensure that you able to exercise your rights regarding Personal Information about you in accordance with applicable law. If you would like to access, erase, or object to, or restrict the processing of Personal Information we collect, you may submit a request to [privacy@schoolday.com](mailto:privacy@schoolday.com)[.](mailto:privacy@schoolday.fi.) We will promptly review all such requests in accordance with applicable laws. Depending on where you live, you may also have a right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority or other regulatory agency if you believe that we have violated any of the rights concerning Personal Information about you. We encourage you to first reach out to us at [privacy@schoolday.com](mailto:privacy@schoolday.com), so we have an opportunity to address your concerns directly before you do so.

**How Long Does School Day Retain Personal Information?**

As a matter of policy, School Day retains Personal Information collected about Users in connection with the Services in an identifiable form in accordance with the terms of the agreements we have in place with our Customers and as long as needed for purposes of performing the Services, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted under the applicable laws. Thereafter, School Day will delete all of the Personal Information in its possession. We may retain non-personal and/or anonymized data generated from your use of the Service.

For California Residents
------------------------

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by School Day to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [privacy@schoolday.com](mailto:privacy@schoolday.com) or write us:

SchoolDay LLC, 7222597

850 New Burton Road  
Suite 201  
Dover DE 19904

Furthermore, California residents have the following rights with respect to Personal Information we may have collected about them:

**(i)      Requests to Know**

You have the right to request that we disclose:

* The categories of Personal Information we have collected about you;
* The categories of Personal Information about you we have sold or disclosed for a business purpose;
* The categories of sources from which we have collected Personal Information about you;
* The business or commercial purposes for selling or collecting Personal Information about you;
* The categories of Personal Information sold or shared about you, as well as the categories of third parties to whom the Personal Information was sold, by category of Personal Information for each party to whom Personal Information was sold; and
* The specific pieces of Personal Information collected.

You may submit a request to know by emailing us at [privacy@schoolday.com](mailto:privacy@schoolday.com). The delivery of our response may take place electronically or by mail. We are not required to respond to requests to know more than twice in a 12-month period. You may also contact the Customer that uses our Services for the purpose of exercising your rights.

**(ii)      Requests to Delete**

You have the right to request that we delete any Personal Information about you that we have collected. Upon receiving a verified request to delete Personal Information, we will do so unless otherwise authorized by law. You may submit a request to delete Personal Information by emailing us at [privacy@schoolday.com](mailto:privacy@schoolday.com).

**(iii)     No Sale of Personal Information**

We do not sell, and have not in the prior 12 months sold, Personal Information about California residents. Therefore, we have not included a “Do Not Sell My Personal Info” link on our Site. If our practices change, we will update this Privacy Statement and take any other necessary action to comply with applicable law.

**(iv)     Authorized Agents**

You may designate an authorized agent to make requests on your behalf. You must provide an authorized agent written permission to submit a request on your behalf, and we may require that you verify your identity directly with us. Alternatively, an authorized agent that has been provided power of attorney pursuant to Probate Code sections 4000-4465 may submit a request on your behalf.

**(v)     Methods for Submitting Consumer Requests and Our Response to Requests**

You may submit a request for access and requests to delete Personal Information about you by emailing us at [privacy@schoolday.com](mailto:privacy@schoolday.com).

Upon receipt of a request, we may ask you for additional Personal Information to verify your identity. Any additional Personal Information you provide will be used only to verify your identity and not for any other purpose.

We will acknowledge the receipt of your request within ten (10) business days of receipt. Subject to our ability to verify your identity, we will respond to your request within 45 calendar days of receipt.

You may also contact the Customer that uses our Services for the purpose of exercising your rights.

**(vi)**     **The Right to Non-Discrimination**

You have the right not to be discriminated against for the exercise of your California privacy rights described above.

Children
--------

Many of the Users of the Services are children under the age of 16 and we provide additional protections with respect to Personal Information we may collect about children in connection with the Services, including:

* Notifying parents about our practices relating to Personal Information about children;
* Where required by law, obtaining consent from parents or Customers, where allowed to act for, in lieu of, or on behalf of, parents, for the collection of Personal Information about children, or for sending information about the Services to children;
* Minimizing the collection of Personal Information about children to no more than is necessary to use the Services; and
* Giving parents and Customers access or the ability to request access to Personal Information we have collected about children and the ability to request that the Personal Information be amended or deleted.

If you have any questions about our practices relating to protection of Personal Information about children, you may contact us at:

SchoolDay LLC, 7222597

850 New Burton Road  
Suite 201  
Dover DE 19904

Security of Personal Information
--------------------------------

We take reasonable and appropriate measures to protect Personal Information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction, taking into account the risks involved in the processing and the nature of the Personal Information. Despite these efforts to store Personal Information collected on and through the Services and otherwise by us in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee the security of Personal Information during its transmission or its storage on our systems. Further, while we attempt to ensure the integrity and security of Personal Information, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third parties such as so-called hackers from illegally obtaining access to Personal Information. We do not warrant or represent that Personal Information about you will be protected against, loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties.

Changes to This Statement
-------------------------

From time to time we may change this Statement. You can tell when changes have been made to the Statement by referring to the “Last Updated” legend on top of this page. Please review this Statement regularly to ensure that you are aware of any changes.

Questions or Concerns?
----------------------

Should you have any questions regarding this Privacy Statement or your privacy, please contact us at [privacy@schoolday.com](mailto:privacy@schoolday.com). We seek to promptly resolve any questions or concerns you may have.

### School Day Scholarship

**SCHOLARSHIP PERIOD TERMS**

I. Introduction. School Day has developed an AI-enhanced School Wellbeing Service for K-12 Education, as further described in Schedule A (the “Service”).

II. **Entire Agreement and Other Terms.** These Terms constitute the sole and entire agreement of School Day and the Customer with respect to the evaluation of the Service, and supersede all prior or contemporaneous understandings, agreements, negotiations, representations and warranties, and communications, both written and oral.

III. **Access to the Service.** In consideration of the provision of the Feedback, during the Scholarship Period, School Day will provide the Customer access to and use of the Service for the Intended Purpose, and for no other purpose, in accordance with these Terms.

IV. **Feedback.** If you provide School Day with any feedback or suggestions regarding the Service (“Feedback”), you hereby assign to School Day all rights in such Feedback and agree that School Day shall have the right to use and fully exploit such Feedback and related information in any manner it deems appropriate.

V. **Termination of Scholarship Period.** For a period of 60 days following the Scholarship Period, School Day will maintain any data entered by Customer in the Service. If Customer desires to continue use of the Service after the Scholarship Period, Customer shall separately execute and deliver School Day’s standard order form and services agreement.

VI. **Definitions.** As used in these Terms:

“Intended Purpose” means the testing and evaluation of the Service.

“Scholarship Period” means the 60 day period commencing on the Effective Date.

“Service” has the meaning set out in Section I.

VII. **Restrictions on Use.** Customer shall not (a) demonstrate, copy, sell, rent, lease, lend, sublicense, distribute, or otherwise transfer or provide access to the Service to any third party; (b) modify, reuse, disassemble, decompile, reverse engineer or otherwise translate any software contained within the Service or any portion thereof; (c) create derivative works based on the Service; or (d) delete, alter, cover, or distort any copyright, trademark, or other proprietary rights notice placed by School Day on or in the Service.

VIII. **Legal Compliance.** Customer and School Day shall each comply with all applicable laws and regulations with respect to the use of the Service

IX. **Intellectual Property.** School Day owns and shall retain all right, title and interest in and to all intellectual property rights embodied in and appertaining to the Service, including, without limitation, all such rights in the software and content, together with all improvements, enhancements, developments, derivative works, and other modifications thereto.

X. **Representations and Warranties.** School Day represents and warrants to Customer that it holds all rights necessary to grant the license set forth herein and to provide the Service during the Scholarship Period as contemplated by these Terms. EXCEPT AS SPECIFICALLY SET FORTH HEREIN, THE SERVICE IS PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. TO THE EXTENT ALLOWED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, ARE HEREBY DISCLAIMED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.

XI. **Limitations on Liability.** To the extent permitted by law, in no event shall either School Day or Customer be liable for any indirect, punitive, or consequential damages, including, but not limited to, lost profits or business opportunities.

XII. **Governing Law.** These Terms shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Finland, excluding its choice of law and conflicts of law provisions, as if executed by residents of Finland.

XIII. **Notices**

**SCHEDULE A**

**Service Description**

### Terms of Use

The Service, hosted by SchoolDay LLC (later called "SchoolDay"), is a centrally maintained web service that can be accessed either through an Internet browser or through standalone applications on the phone.

The service is primarily intended for use by educational institutions and individual pupils and teachers, but can also be used by families.

The service includes e.g. Wellbeing service and Dashboard solution. These Terms of Use apply to your use of the Service described above (the "Service"). The Terms and Conditions govern the relationship between the Service Provider and the Service Users (hereinafter also referred to as the “User”). The Service is owned by the Service Provider and the User is granted access to the Service in accordance with these Terms of Use.

By registering with and/or using the Service, you agree to these terms and agree to abide by them. If you do not agree to these terms, you will not be able to use the Service. Further, the User shall comply with the applicable laws, other applicable regulations and good practice when using the Service.

### DATA PROTECTION

The Service Provider shall comply with applicable law when processing personal data. More detailed information on the processing of personal data can be found in the privacy statement that the User registering for / using the Service must read.

### REGISTRATION AND USER ID

There are two ways for a user to obtain a username, either:

1. by registering for the Service by themselves

OR

1. The user who purchased the service has registered the user.

The User will have access to the Service with a password and username to enable the User to log into the Service. The user account associated with the user account must not contain offensive or incitement to criminal activity and should otherwise be in good standing.

When registering for and using the Service, the User must truthfully and accurately disclose all information required by the User. The Service Provider may exercise its right under section 10 of these Terms of Use to lock or delete a User's Account if the User has attempted to mislead the Service Provider.

Users are responsible for activities performed under their own account. The username and password are personal and may not be disclosed to third parties. If the password or username is disclosed to third parties, the User must immediately inform the representative of his / her own institution or the Service Provider.

### DATA STORAGE AND BACKUP

The Service User may store the material on the Service Provider's server. However, the Service Provider does not guarantee the preservation of the stored data and is not responsible for any damage that may occur due to alteration, loss, destruction or deletion of the data. In order to preserve the information, the Service User is responsible for storing backup copies of the data and material stored on the Service Provider's server.

### RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR USE OF THE SERVICE AND FOR THE USER-PROVIDED CONTENT

The Service User is solely responsible for any material that he or she uploads to the Service and / or makes available to others through the Service (including, but not limited to, downloading material to the Service, using various linking methods, and in any other manner). The Service Provider does not actively review the User Submissions to the Service and therefore does not take any responsibility for the content of the materials. The Service may not transmit or store on the Service Provider's server:

* Which infringes on the copyrights or other rights of third parties 
* Which infringes, degrades, harasses or threatens someone 
* Which interferes with the operation of the service 
* Which is otherwise contrary to the law or good practice in force in Finland.

The Service may not be used for commercial purposes.

Any user of the Service who notices material added to the Service in violation of these Terms of Use or otherwise notices that the Service has been used in violation of these Terms of Use shall immediately notify the Service Provider.

### RIGHTS FOR USER-CREATED CONTENT

These Terms of Use do not affect the proprietary rights of any material you submit to the Service, and the rights remain with their rightful owners. Under these Terms of Service, the Service Provider does not acquire any rights to the above material other than those required by the Service Provider to execute the Service in accordance with the Terms of Service.

Example: An image uploaded to the Service will be redistributed in its original or edited version to other Users of the Service in accordance with the specified publicity for the image. The different versions can be manufactured and distributed via third-party proxy servers, for example, to improve performance.

In addition, the Service Provider may exercise its rights under section 10 (“Consequences of Non-Compliance with Terms of Use”) (including removing material that violates the Terms of Use from the Service).

### CHANGING THE TERMS OF USE

The Service Provider has the right to unilaterally change these Terms of Use at any time. Changes to the Terms of Use will be communicated to us separately as deemed appropriate. The Service User accepts the changed Terms of Use by using the Service after being informed of the changed Terms of Use.

### SERVICE MAINTENANCE AND UPDATES

School Day strives to provide the most reliable Service possible and is available 24 hours a day by default. However, School Day makes no warranty as to the operation or features of the Service.

School Day is constantly striving to improve the Service and may make changes to the Service. You acknowledge and agree that the development and modification of the Service, in whole or in part, is the sole responsibility of School Day.

### INTERRUPTION OF THE SERVICE

School Day will not be liable for damages resulting from technical failure, maintenance work, upgrades, communications, Internet outages, or other eventualities caused by disruption of the Service.

### CONSEQUENCES OF CONDUCT OF THE TERMS OF USE

School Day has the right to remove or block any material distributed through the Service that is deemed by School Day to be in violation of the rules and principles contained in these Terms of Use.

In addition, the Service Provider has the right to lock or delete the user account of the Service user in the event that the User violates its obligations under these terms of use (for example, by uploading material that violates the terms of use.

Upon becoming aware of the violation, the Service Provider may immediately lock the user account / ID. As a result, the Service user who committed the infringement will no longer be able to log into their user account.

### APPLICABLE LAW AND DISPUTE SETTLEMENT

These terms shall be governed by the laws of Finland. Any disputes arising from the terms shall be resolved primarily by negotiation. If no settlement is reached, the dispute will be settled in the Uusimaa District Court.

SCHOOL DAY SERVICES DATA SHEET
------------------------------

This Privacy Statement applies to all Services provided by School Day Helsinki Ltd (hereinafter "School Day")

By using the Services, you consent to the processing of your personal data by us, either as a controller or on behalf of the controller, depending on the Service. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, do not install or use our Services.

School Day reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Services indicates that you have accepted the changes to this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions or inquiries regarding the Privacy Statement and the data subject's rights, you may contact us:

SchoolDay LLC, 7222597

850 New Burton Road  
Suite 201  
Dover DE 19904

### WHAT INFORMATION WE PROCESS IN THE SERVICE

When you use the School Day Services, we process information about you.

The information we process about you may include but is not limited to, an email address, a device ID, an IP address, usernames, and passwords.

When you use the Services, we also store information about your use of the Service, such as answering questions.

### ANALYTICS

School Day uses your data to perform visitor tracking and data analysis and to enable third-party analytics. We use the information we analyze to support our business analysis and overall operations, as well as business intelligence, product development, product and service improvement, and content customization. School Day may also use third parties to develop and analyze the use of the Services.

### DISCLOSURE AND TRANSFER OF PERSONAL DATA

School Day will not share your personal information with third parties, nor will it be transferred outside the European Union or the EEA.

### DATA RETENTION AND ACCURACY

School Day will retain the information it collects on behalf of the controller for as long as it is necessary under the Agreement with the controller unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. Thereafter, School Day will delete all of the above information in its possession, except for non-personal and/or anonymized data generated from your use of the Service. School Day cannot spontaneously verify the accuracy of personal data, it has been obtained from the data controller.

School Day may use non-personal and/or anonymized information generated from your use of the Service even after you have removed your personal information.

Some of the information may be retained for a longer period of time if such retention is necessary to resolve disputes, enforce School Day Agreements, or comply with technical and legal requirements relating to information security, data integrity, and operation of the Services.

### SECURITY

School Day applies industry-standard standards and maintains appropriate security measures to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of information held by it.

### FURTHERMORE

Any information you provide through public channels or similar forums on the Service will become public information and may not be subject to privacy or confidentiality requirements.

### SPECIAL NOTICE ON PRIVATE CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

School Day services are aimed at users in the school world, where a large proportion of children are children. School Day understands the need to provide special protection for users who are children. For this reason, we will pay particular attention to the proper processing of the information contained in the Service.

### School Day Customer register

**PRIVACY POLICY**
==================

SCHOOL DAY CUSTOMER AND CONTACT DATA
------------------------------------

As with virtually all companies, we also have a register of customers and people interested in our services. However, you have no cause for concern, because we only collect the necessary information and nothing else. In addition, we keep our data security to the best of our ability to keep the stored data safe. You also have the opportunity at any time to ask for your information to be displayed, and you can ask at any time to correct incorrect information. Naturally, you can also ask us to destroy all your information at any time.

Below you will find a more detailed description of our operations and your rights in relation to our customer and contact records.

**REGISTER KEEPER**:
--------------------

SchoolDay LLC, 7222597

850 New Burton Road  
Suite 201  
Dover DE 19904

**RESPONSIBLE FOR DATA PROTECTION:**
------------------------------------

Juha Engman, tel. +358 44 753 2990, [info@schoolday.com](mailto:info@schoolday.com)

**REGISTERED:**
---------------

The register addresses the personal data of SchoolDay LLC (hereinafter referred to as “the Company”) and potential customer representatives.

**WHAT DATA WE COLLECT AND WHY:**
---------------------------------

The purpose of processing personal data is, in particular, for the existing customers of the Company to handle and maintain customer relations. Personal data are also processed for the sale and direct marketing of the Company’s products and services and for the Company’s information activities.

The purpose of personal information regarding potential customers is to direct marketing and other sales and marketing activities of the Company’s services and products.

The processing ground is, as the case may be, a legitimate interest based on the Company’s use, in particular marketing, and, in the case of customers, a contractual relationship with the Company.

**PERSONAL DATA PROCESSED:**
----------------------------

In its customer register, the company processes the following personal information from its customers or their potential customers:

* name, gender, date of birth and title;
* contact details (email address, phone number, address);
* company name, business ID and address details and
* customer relationship information (username, ordering and usage information, billing information)
* Classification information provided by a person himself (eg decision-maker – IT specialist or business decision-maker).

**REGULAR SOURCES OF INFORMATION:**
-----------------------------------

Personal data is collected from registered ones (for example, by phone, email or through the online channels owned or maintained by the Company), as well as on the registration of the services and on the use of the services.

Personal information may also be obtained from external marketing service providers and the participant’s information on events organized by the Company. Updates to personal information may also be obtained from authorities and companies providing update services.

**REGULAR DELIVERIES AND TRANSFER OF PERSONAL DATA:**
-----------------------------------------------------

Your personal information may be transferred to the Company’s sales and marketing partners who may process your personal information only for marketing purposes on behalf of the Company. We always ensure that our affiliates do not process transferable personal data for any other purpose.

**TRANSFER OF PERSONAL DATA OUTSIDE THE EU / EEA TERRITORY:**
-------------------------------------------------------------

In certain cases, we will transfer your personal data outside the European Union or the European Economic Area, in accordance with the Personal Data Processing Act, to the following parties: If you have, for example, uploaded material, registered for the event or made a contact request on our website (www.schoolday.fi), where we use MailChimp Inc. service in USA, the Transfer Criterion in this respect is Privacy Shield (for more information, [https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome)).

**STORAGE TIME OF PERSONAL DATA:**
----------------------------------

Your personal information will be retained as long as the customer relationship is in effect. After the customer relationship expires, personal data will be retained for a maximum of two years after the end of the customer relationship. Personal data may be kept longer if the applicable law or the contractual obligations of the Company for third parties require longer retention periods.

The personal data of potential customers will be maintained as long as the registrar is engaged in positions where the product or service marketed relates, provided that the registrar has not denied direct marketing. However, information on the denial of direct marketing may be retained. Personal data may be kept longer if the applicable law or the contractual obligations of the Company for third parties requiring longer retention periods.

**REGISTRANT RIGHTS:**
----------------------

You have the right at any time to object to the processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes. A registered user can give the Company consents and bans on channel-specific direct marketing (for example, prohibit e-mail marketing messages but allow marketing messages sent by letter).

At any time, the data subject has the right, under applicable data protection law:

* get information about the processing of his/her personal data;
* have access to their personal information and verify the personal data processed by the Company;
* to demand correction and supplementation of inaccurate and incorrect personal data;
* require the removal of their personal data;
* object to the processing of his / her personal data on a basis related to his or her personal situation, insofar as the processing of personal data is the legitimate interest of the Company;
* obtaining personal data in a formatted format and transferring such information to another registrar provided that the person has personally provided the personal data to the Company, the Company processes such personal data on the basis of the agreement and the processing is carried out automatically; and
* require the processing of personal data to be restricted.

The registrar must submit a request for execution of the aforementioned right in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Statement. The company may apply to register to confirm its request in writing and to confirm the registered identity before processing the request. The company may refuse to execute the request on the basis of the applicable law.

**THE RIGHT TO COMPLAIN TO THE SUPERVISORY AUTHORITY:**
-------------------------------------------------------

Each registrant has the right to file a complaint with the supervisory authority concerned or with the supervisory authority of the EU Member State where the registered resident or work is located if the registrar considers that the Company has not processed the personal data in accordance with applicable data protection legislation.

**SECURITY:**
-------------

The registry is protected by personal passwords. In addition, the register is governed by the Company’s general information security principles regarding information contained in information systems. The customer and contact registers are only allowed to deal with the employees who are specifically appointed for the job.

**COOKIES:**
------------

The company’s website uses cookies. A cookie is a commonly used small text file that your web browser stores on your computer or other terminal when you visit a web site. The browser will send you your information back to the webpage when you visit it again. All modern web pages use cookies to provide you with a personalized browser experience.

**CONTACT:**
------------

Requests to use Registered Rights, questions about this Privacy Statement, and other contact information should be sent to [info@schoolday.com.](mailto:info@schoolday.com) The registered person may also contact you personally or in writing at the address below:

SchoolDay LLC, 7222597

850 New Burton Road  
Suite 201  
Dover DE 19904

**AMENDMENTS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY:**
--------------------------------------

This privacy statement can be updated from time to time, for example, as legislation changes. 

### School Day Web Pages

COOKIES AND OTHER WEB SITE USAGE MONITORING
-------------------------------------------

We use cookies on our website. In order for the pages and services to work properly, you should allow cookies. Below you will find out more about the purposes for which cookies are collected and how you can influence the management of cookies.

WHAT ARE COOKIES?
-----------------

Cookies allow websites to track your interest in the items on which websites you have visited and what you have viewed on the site. In practice, cookies are small text files that your web browser stores on your device. These cookies contain a unique identifier that identifies your browser. Information is collected on the visited pages and cookies do not contain personal information.

SITE COOKIES
------------

We use cookies to monitor and analyze the use of our pages. Through cookies we collect information about how many people use our services, how long they spend time on our site and what they are looking in our site. Cookies also tell us how you came to the School Day website and where you go from the website. Information is used to develop our products and services.

THIRD-PARTY COOKIES
-------------------

School Day sites use also third-party cookies, which means in practice that the School Day partners may set cookies on your computer when you visit our company website. We obtain from these service providers, for example, reporting and analytics tools that provide information we use in our own operations. Our services also include so-called community links such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn and Instagram. If you have allowed the use of cookies in community-based services, it is possible that these providers will collect similar information about your actions on the School Day website.

BLOCKING COOKIES AND BLOCKING THEM
----------------------------------

You can actually influence what cookies you want to accept. In practice, you can do this through your own browser settings. You can block cookies completely, but you may not be able to use all pages and services as intended. However, cookies can be removed at regular intervals, and by doing this it is not possible to create a long-term user profile when website needs to start creating it from the beginning in the absence of baseline data. The third option is to limit the use of cookies by excluding third-party cookies from the allowed list.

Contact Us
----------

SchoolDay LLC

info@schoolday.com

Who We Are
----------

_We handle data responsibly. [Read our privacy statement](https://www.schoolday.com/en/about/privacy). By submitting any form, you agree that we will store and process the information you provide in accordance with our privacy policy._

What We Do
----------

### Main menu

×

Please enter your email and name, so we will send you the content you requested!

 Invalid Input

 Invalid Input
